shellshock.io 2019-10-30

# Privacy Policy - Blue Wizard Digital

Updated: May 24th 2018

**Key Points:**

  * We collect personal information and the type of information we collect depends on what products you use and how you use them. 
  * Blue Wizard Digital (referred to as us/we/our in this Privacy Policy) is the Data Controller of data processed through your use of its services.
  * You have the right to access your personal information. You may contact our Data Protection Officer (data-controller[at]bluewizard.com) at any time with inquiries about your personal data, to update your personal data, or to request that we delete your personal data. 
  * This Privacy Policy explains how and what personal data relating to you we may use in relation to our website [www.bluewizard.com](https://bluewizard.com/) (“Site”), our apps and any games, products, forums and services we offer through the apps or Website or other dedicated websites (such as [https://shellshock.io/](https://shellshock.io/) and any other .io games which may be offered by us from time to time) or otherwise provided by us (all collectively referred to in this Privacy Policy as our “Services”).
  * The type and nature of the data includes profile and contact details, data relating to your use of the services including game stats, posts, log in, traffic data, data relating to the device you use to access the services.
  * We use your data to provide and personalise the Services, for marketing and ads, and to respond to queries and monitor use of our services.
  * We may send you marketing materials relating to other services we think may be of interest to you which you can opt out of at any time. We don’t give or sell your data to third parties for them to market to you.

It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our Site and delivering Services. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Please do not use the Services if you do not agree to this Privacy Policy.

Please note that the Services may contain links to websites or other services owned and operated by third parties. We do not endorse any such third-party services. We are not responsible or liable for anything that happens to you when you visit or use these services. We strongly recommends that you review the privacy policies and cookie usage of these third parties.  

By using the Blue Wizard Site and/or Services you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and, as applicable, Blue Wizard’s EULA. 

For questions and information about Privacy Policy and data subject’s rights, please contact us at data-controller[at]bluewizard.com. 

All Blue Wizard Services are governed by this Privacy Policy and by using or accessing a Service you give consent to the processing, use and disclosure of your data. Please do not install or use the Services if you do not agree to this Privacy Policy. 

Blue Wizard reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of Services will signify your acceptance of the changes to this Privacy Policy.

## 1\. Information We Collect 

In this Privacy Policy “data” means any personal data about you which could identify you (by itself or in combination with other data) such as your name, address or email address.

Likely situations when you are making personal information available to Blue Wizard include, but are not limited to: (i) by using Blue Wizard’s mobile apps or visiting our websites, (ii) registration for Services, contests and special events; (iii) accessing Services using a third party ID, such as social networking sites or gaming services; (iv) subscribing to newsletters; (v) purchasing a product or services through Blue Wizard’s online stores or within the app (or “in-app purchase”); (vi) using “tell a friend,” “email this page,” or other similar features; (vii) requesting technical support; and (viii) otherwise through use of Blue Wizard Services where personal data is required for use and/or participation.

**We may collect the following data about you:**  
**Data you give us directly:**

  * if you register with us (such as your date of birth, username, avatar, password and email address) that you provide by entering any competitions or completing any surveys, including your scores and ranking in any competition;
  * information you provide by completing any in-game purchases, such as buying in-game currency and other items;
  * information you provide by participating in any Blue Wizard chat forums or social media functions; and
  * information you provide us if you report a problem with any Services.

**Data we may collect when you use our Services (whether or not you register with us):**

  * data about your location, device type, operating system and platform; 
  * data about your computer’s browser version, operating system version, page loading time, network, generated device identifier information, hashed MAC address, referral source and IP address
  * data generated through playing games such as your high score and rankings;  
game play history;
  * the number of times you visit our Services and the amount of time you spend using the Services; and
  * where you are accessing Services through a third-party account such as Facebook or Google – certain information relating to your account with those third parties including your name, user ID, gender, location (country and/or city specific), email address, date of birth, information from your public profile including friends and connections, log in details, avatar, gender and other information based on your use of our Services.  

Blue Wizard may supplement your data with data received from third parties in connection with demographic, advertisement, market and other analytics surveys or services.

## 2\. Contact for the Data Protection Officer   

Blue Wizard Digital  
Suite 250, 1829 Beaufort Avenue  
Comox, BC  
V9M 1R9  
Email: data-controller[at]bluewizard.com  
Website: https://www.bluewizard.com  
  
Any data subject may, at any time, contact our Data Protection Officer directly with all questions and suggestions concerning data protection. Blue Wizard will need sufficient information from you to establish your identity and to verify your access request, and also to assist us in handling your request.

## 3\. Ad Serving Technology

Blue Wizard reserves the right to use and disclose the collected, non-personal (anonymized) data for purposes of advertising by Blue Wizard or Blue Wizard’s partners and contractors.

Blue Wizard may employ third party ad serving technologies that use certain methods to collect information as a result of ad serving through Services.

Blue Wizard or third parties operating the ad serving technology may use demographic and geo-location information (for more information regarding use of Location Data see below Section 3) as well as information logged from your hardware or device to ensure that relevant advertising is presented within the Service. Blue Wizard or third parties may collect and use data, for such purposes, including but not limited to, data such as IP address, Device ID, MAC address, installed software, application usage data, hardware type, Operating System information, browser information, unique identifiers in browser cookies, Flash cookies, and HTML5 local storage, Internet and on-line usage information and in-game information.

The foregoing data may be used and disclosed in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the privacy policy of the company providing the ad serving technology.

Blue Wizard may display to you behaviourally targeted advertising. If you wish to “opt out” of certain targeted advertising, please visit [http://www.youradchoices.com](http://www.youradchoices.com/) and/or [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). Please note that the links above may not reach all Blue Wizard’s advertising partners and certain behaviourally targeted advertising may still be displayed to you. If you want to be certain that no behaviourally targeted advertisements are displayed to you, please do not use or access the Services.

Some services may include the use of in-game advertisements or brand placement. Such ads or sponsorships will be noted as such within the services.

Additionally please note that if you “opt out” it does not mean that you will no longer receive advertising. It just means that the advertising you see displayed will not be customized to you and your interests and may be less relevant to you.

## 4\. Location Data

To the extent Blue Wizard makes location enabled Services available and you use such Services, Blue Wizard may collect and process your location data to provide location related Services and advertisements. For example, some add-ons or offers may be available at dedicated locations. The location data is processed  and stored only for the duration that is required for the provision of the location related Services.

Blue Wizard may use, depending on the service (1)IP-based location based on the IP address presented by the end-user, (2) fine geo-location data based on coordinates obtained from a mobile device’s GPS radio, or (3) coarse, network-based geo-location data based on proximity of network towers or the location of WiFi networks.

Your fine, GPS-based geo-location is not accessed without your consent. Notwithstanding Blue Wizard’s partners who are providing location related parts of the Service, Blue Wizard will not share your GPS geo-location with third parties without your consent. To the extent Blue Wizard makes available GPS geo-location to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy, it will be provided anonymously.

## 5\. Analytics

Blue Wizard uses your information to perform its own analytics and to enable analytics provided by third parties.  We use analytical information for supporting business analysis and operations, business intelligence, product development, improving products and services, personalizing content, providing advertising, and making recommendations.   Blue Wizard may also use third-parties, such as Facebook, Google, Unity Analytics and Appsflyer to process anonymous analytics data.

## 6\. Disclosure and Transfer of Personal Data

Personal data may be disclosed to third parties including third parties located outside the European Union or the European Economic Area in accordance with applicable legislation and this Privacy Policy.

Blue Wizard may use third parties to collect and process personal data on Blue Wizard’s behalf and in according to Blue Wizard’s instructions. Blue Wizard is not liable for the acts and omissions of these third parties, except as provided by mandatory law.

## 7\. Data Retention and Correctness

Blue Wizard retains the collected data for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. Thereafter Blue Wizard deletes all aforementioned data in its possession within a reasonable timeframe. Blue Wizard does not verify the correctness of personal data.

Please note that some data may be further retained if necessary to resolve disputes, enforce Blue Wizard user agreements, and comply with technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of Services.

## 8\. Cookies, beacons and tracking

The Services may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags, local shared objects, hardware-based device identifiers, Operating System-based identifiers, clear GIFs and web beacons. Blue Wizard treats information collected by cookies and similar technologies as non-personal data.

Cookies: A “cookie” is a small file stored by your browser when told to do so by a website. Typically websites place a number of different cookies on an end-user’s machine. Some of the cookies are “1st Party,” from the website itself, and others are “3rd party,” belonging to advertising and analytics entities or social networks.  Blue Wizard’s cookies do not include personal data and are typically used to quickly identify your device and to “remember” your browser during subsequent visits for purposes of functionality, preferences, and website performance. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your device; however, disabling cookies may affect your ability to use the Services.

Flash cookies & HTML5: Blue Wizard may also use Flash cookies (local shared objects) and HTML5 local storage. Flash cookies are small files similar to browser cookies, but which are not stored in the browser and can also be used to remember your settings, to personalize the look and feel of the Services, or for advertising and analytics. You may prevent Flash cookies from being stored by following the instructions provided by Adobe at http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html.

Web Beacons and pixel tags: A “web beacon” or a “pixel tag” is an electronic image (often not visible to the end-user) that allows Blue Wizard to count users who have visited certain pages or viewed certain advertisements. Additionally, e-mails and other electronic communications Blue Wizard sends to you may contain pixel tags that enable Blue Wizard to track your usage of the communication, including whether the communication was opened and/or what links were followed, if any.

## 9\. Third Party Terms and Conditions

Please note that your access to and use of the Services may be subject to certain third party terms and conditions and Blue Wizard is not liable for any such third parties’ use of your personal data.

Certain Services that Blue Wizard may offer, such as multiplayer gaming, social networking and gaming console services, may use third party services to provide authentication for the Services with a gaming console ID, social networking ID, or gaming network account. In connection with such use, certain personally identifiable user and/or membership data may be transferred automatically to and from Blue Wizard.

Blue Wizard may disclose your personal data to third parties in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of Blue Wizard’s stock and/or assets or other corporate change, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process provided, however, that this Privacy Policy shall continue to govern such personal data.

## 10\. Safeguards

Blue Wizard follows generally accepted industry standards and maintains reasonable safeguards to attempt to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information in Blue Wizard’s possession.

We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the data we hold.

We use industry-standard practices such as encryption, physically secured rooms, firewalls and password protection systems to safeguard the confidentiality of any personal information that we might collect from you. For example, your email address and password will be encrypted which will make it extra hard for someone to discover and use them. We also strive to limit access to your data to employees performing a legitimate business function. We review our security procedures periodically to consider appropriate new technology and updated methods.  
Whilst we will do our best to protect your data, the transmission of information by you to us is not completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of your data. Any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your data, we will use the procedures and security features outlined in this section to try to prevent any unauthorised access.

## 11\. Other

You may choose to disclose data about yourself in the course of contributing user generated content to the Services.

Any data that you disclose in any of these forums, blogs, chats or the like will become public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality with respect to that data.

Blue Wizard may store and/or transfer your personal data to its affiliates and partners in and outside of EU/EEA member states and the United States in accordance with mandatory legislation and this Privacy Policy.

## 12\. Special Note about Children’s Privacy

Blue Wizard does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If Blue Wizard learns that Blue Wizard has inadvertently gathered personal data from children under 13 years of age, Blue Wizard will take reasonable measures to promptly delete such personal data from Blue Wizard’s records.

Blue Wizard understands the need to provide extra privacy protections to users who are children. To that end, features and services such as social networking plug-ins, behaviourally targeted advertising, and collection of data for the purpose of building user profiles are not available to users under 13. Blue Wizard also does not allow our third party partners who engage in such practices to access personally identifiable data from users under 13.

Blue Wizard and its partners do collect non-personally identifiable data from children. This includes, for example, collection of IP-based geolocation data to ensure that the product, service or features served comply with applicable laws of that nation.

## 13\. Disclaimer about third parties

Blue Wizard and its partners also collect data to assess general information about the use of products, such as the number of visitors to our sites and services and which sections of a site or service are popular. Blue Wizard also uses this data to provide contextually-relevant advertising to users, to prevent users from seeing the same ad repeatedly, and to allow users to personalize their experience on the site or service (for example, to save a high score in a game). Blue Wizard and its partners may also use cookies, pixels, hardware-based identifiers, Operating System-based identifiers, and software-set identifiers, to manage and measure the performance of advertising.

Please note that Blue Wizard’s partners may have their own policies related to tracking technologies for analytics and ad-serving purposes.  While Blue Wizard requires that companies comply with Blue Wizard’s privacy policy before Blue Wizard allows those companies to access our sites and services, Blue Wizard does not actually control third-party data collection and use. Blue Wizard encourages parents to review the list of operators below and to become familiar with those parties policies and practices.

**Disclaimer about the Ad technology providers**

We may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support and maintain our website. Depending on the ads that are served, your data may be shared with any of the ad technology provider listed below. Ad technology providers (including Google, Ad Exchanges, SSPs, DSPs, ad networks, bidders and vendors) use your data for example, to show you personalized ads or to report on conversions. In the overview below you can find links to information on how the technology providers use your data.

**Ad technology providers**

Further info on how the ad technology providers use your data:

Google https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/

Aarki http://corp.aarki.com/privacy

Adacado https://www.adacado.com/privacy-policy-april-25-2018/

Adara Media https://adara.com/2018/04/10/adara-gdpr-faq/

AdClear https://www.adclear.de/datenschutzerklaerung/

ADEX http://theadex.com

Adform https://site.adform.com/uncategorized/product-and-services-privacy-policy/

Adikteev https://www.adikteev.com/eu/privacy/

AdLedge https://adledge.com/data-privacy/

Adloox http://adloox.com/disclaimer

Adludio https://adludio.com/termsandconditions

AdMaxim http://www.admaxim.com/admaxim-privacy-policy/

Admedo https://www.admedo.com/privacy-policy

Admetrics https://admetrics.io/en/privacy_policy/

Adobe Advertising Cloud https://www.adobe.com/privacy/general-data-protection-regulation.html

AdRoll, Inc. https://www.adroll.com/gdpr

AdTriba https://privacy.adtriba.com/

advanced STORE GmbH https://www.ad4mat.com/en/privacy/

Adventori https://www.adventori.com/fr/avec-nous/mentions-legales/

advolution.control http://advolution.de/privacy.php

affilinet https://www.affili.net/uk/footeritem/privacy-policy

Akamai http://www.akamai.com/compliance/privacy

Amazon https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010

Amobee https://www.amobee.com/trust/privacy-guidelines

Analights https://analights.com/docs/analights-consent-to-the-processing-of-personal-data-en.pdf

AppLovin Corp. https://www.applovin.com/privacy

AppNexus https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy

Arrivalist https://www.arrivalist.com/privacy#gdpr

AudienceProject http://privacy.audienceproject.com/for-users/

Aunica http://www.aunica.com/privacy/privacy.html

Avocet http://avocet.io/privacy-portal

Batch Media http://batch.ba/datenschutzerklarung/

BDSK Handels GmbH & Co. KG https://www.xxxlutz.de/ocms/privacy

Beeswax https://www.beeswax.com/privacy.html

Betgenius http://betting.geniussports.com/connextra-service-terms-conditions/

Bidswitch http://www.bidswitch.com/privacy-policy/

Blismedia http://www.blis.com/privacy/

Bombora http://bombora.com/privacy

Booking.com https://www.booking.com/content/privacy.en-gb.html

C3 Metrics https://c3metrics.com/privacy

Cablato http://cablato.com/privacy

Celtra https://www.celtra.com/privacy-policy/

Centro https://www.centro.net/privacy-policy/

Cint https://www.cint.com/participant-privacy-notice/

Clinch https://clinch.co/pages/privacy.html

Cloud Technologies http://green.erne.co/assets/PolicyCT.pdf

Cloudflare https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/

Commanders Act https://www.commandersact.com/en/privacy/

comScore https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy

Conversant/CJ Affiliate https://www.conversantmedia.eu/legal/privacy-policy

Crimtan https://crimtan.com/privacy-ctl/

Criteo https://www.criteo.com/privacy/

CUBED http://cubed.ai/privacy-policy/gdpr/

DataXu https://www.dataxu.com/gdpr/

Delta Projects http://www.deltaprojects.com/data-collection-policy/

Demandbase https://www.demandbase.com/privacy-policy/

DENTSU http://www.dentsu.co.jp/terms/data_policy.html

Dentsu Aegis Network http://www.dentsu.com/termsofuse/data_policy.html

Digiseg http://www.digiseg.io/GDPR/

DMA Institute https://www.dma-institute.com/privacy-compliancy/

DoubleVerify https://www.doubleverify.com/privacy/

Dstillery https://dstillery.com/privacy-policy/

DTS https://client.adhslx.com/privacy.html

EASYmedia https://www.rvty.net/gdpr

eBay https://www.ebay.com/help/policies/member-behaviour-policies/user-privacy-notice-privacy-

policy?id=4260#section12

ebuilders http://ebuilders.nl/privacy

Effinity https://www.effiliation.com/politique-confidentialite.html

emetriq https://www.emetriq.com/datenschutz/

Ensighten https://www.ensighten.com/privacy-policy/

Essens https://essens.no/privacy-policy/

ESV https://www.wizaly.com/terms-of-use#privacy-policy

Evidon https://www.evidon.com/resources/privacy-statement/

Exactag https://www.exactag.com/en/data-privacy/

Exponential http://exponential.com/privacy/

Facebook https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update

Flashtalking http://www.flashtalking.com/privacypolicy/

Fractional Media https://www.fractionalmedia.com/privacy-policy

FUSIO BY S4M http://www.s4m.io/privacy-policy/

Gemius https://www.gemius.com/cookie-policy.html

GfK [https://sensic.net/](https://sensic.net/)

GP One http://www.gsi-one.org/templates/gsi/en/files/privacy_policy.pdf

gskinner https://createjs.com/legal/privacy.html

Haensel AMS https://haensel-ams.com/data-privacy/

Havas Media France – DBi http://www.centraltag.com/commercial/policy/index.action

hurra.com http://www.hurra.com/impressum

IBM https://www.ibm.com/customer-engagement/digital-marketing/gdpr

Ignition One https://www.ignitionone.com/privacy-policy/gdpr-subject-access-requests/

Impact https://impact.com/privacy-policy/

Index Exchange http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/

Infectious Media https://impressiondesk.com/

Innovid http://www.innovid.com/privacy-policy

Integral Ad Science http://www.integralads.com/privacy-policy

intelliAd https://www.intelliad.de/datenschutz

Interpublic Group https://www.interpublic.com/privacy-notice

Jivox http://www.jivox.com/privacy/

Kantar https://www.kantarmedia.com/global/privacy-statement

Kochava https://www.kochava.com/support-privacy/

LifeStreet http://www.lifestreet.com/privacy

Liftoff https://liftoff.io/privacy-policy/

LiveRamp https://liveramp.com/service-privacy-policy/

Localsensor https://www.localsensor.com/privacy.html

LoopMe https://loopme.com/privacy/

Lotame https://www.lotame.com/about-lotame/privacy/

Macromill group https://www.metrixlab.com/privacy-statement/

MainADV http://www.mainad.com/privacy-policy

Manage.com https://www.manage.com/privacy-policy/

Marketing Science Consulting Group, Inc. http://mktsci.com/privacy_policy.htm

MBR Targeting Gmbh https://privacy.mbr-targeting.com

MediaMath http://www.mediamath.com/privacy-policy/

Meetrics https://www.meetrics.com/en/data-privacy/

MindTake Research https://www.mindtake.com/en/reppublika-privacy-policy

Mobitrans http://www.mobitrans.net/privacy-policy/

Mobpro http://mobpro.com/privacy.html

Moloco Ads http://www.molocoads.com/private-policy.html

MSI-ACI http://site.msi-aci.com/Home/FlexTrackPrivacy

Nano Interactive http://www.nanointeractive.com/privacy

Navegg https://www.navegg.com/en/privacy-policy/

Neodata Group https://www.neodatagroup.com/en/security-policy

NEORY GmbH https://www.neory.com/privacy.html

Netflix http://www.netflix.com/google-3PAS-info

Netquest https://www.nicequest.com/us/privacy

Neuralone https://web.neural.one/privacy-policy/

Neustar https://www.home.neustar/privacy

Nielsen http://www.nielsen.com/us/en/privacy-statement/digital-measurement.html

Nordic Factory Solutions AB https://www.bannerflow.com/privacy

numberly http://ads.1000mercis.com/us.html

Oath https://policies.oath.com/xw/en/oath/privacy/enterprise/b2bprivacypolicy/

Objective Partners https://www.objectivepartners.com/cookie-policy-and-privacy-statement/

Omnicom Media Grouphttps://www.omnicommediagroup.com/disclaimer.htm

On Device Research https://ondeviceresearch.com/GDPR

OneTag https://www.onetag.net/privacy/

OpenX Technologies https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/

Optomaton http://optomaton.com/privacy.html

Oracle Data Cloud https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/marketing-cloud-data-cloud-privacy-policy.html

OTTO https://www.otto.de/shoppages/service/about/datenschutzinformation/aboutprivacyneedtoknow

PERMODO http://permodo.com/de/privacy.html

Pixalate http://www.pixalate.com/privacypolicy/

Platform161 https://platform161.com/cookie-and-privacy-policy/

PMG https://www.pmg.com/privacy-policy/

Protected Media http://www.protected.media/privacy-policy/

Publicis Groupe https://www.publicismedia.de/datenschutz/

PubMatic https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy-policy/

PulsePoint https://www.pulsepoint.com/privacy-policy

Quantcast https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/

Rackspace http://www.rackspace.com/gdpr

Rakuten Marketing https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy

Refined Labs https://www.refinedlabs.com/datenschutz-rfa

Relay42 https://relay42.com/privacy

Remerge http://remerge.io/privacy-policy.html

Resonate https://www.resonate.com/privacy-policy/

RevJet https://www.revjet.com/privacy

RhythmOne LLC https://www.rhythmone.com/landing/gdpr

RN SSI Group https://www.valuedopinions.co.uk/privacy

Roq.ad https://www.roq.ad/privacy-policy

RTB House https://www.rtbhouse.com/gdpr/

Rubicon Project http://rubiconproject.com/rubicon-project-yield-optimization-privacy-policy/

Salesforce DMP https://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/

Scenestealer http://www.scenestealer.tv/privacy-policy

Scoota http://scoota.com/privacy-policy/

Seenthis https://seenthis.co/privacy-notice-2018-04-18.pdf

Semasio GmbH http://www.semasio.com/privacy-policy/

SFR http://www.sfr.fr/securite-confidentialite.html

Sift Media https://www.sift.co/privacy

Simpli.fi https://www.simpli.fi/site-privacy-policy2/

Sizmek https://www.sizmek.com/privacy-policy/

Smaato https://www.smaato.com/privacy/

Smadex http://smadex.com/end-user-privacy-policy/

Smart http://smartadserver.com/company/privacy-policy/

Smartology https://www.smartology.net/privacy-policy/

Sociomantic https://www.sociomantic.com/privacy/en/

Sojern https://www.sojern.com/privacy/product-privacy-policy/

Sovrn https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/

Spotad http://www.spotad.co/privacy-policy/

SpotX https://www.spotx.tv/privacy-policy/

TabMo http://static.tabmo.io.s3.amazonaws.com/privacy-policy/index.html

Taboola https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy

TACTICTM Real- Time Marketing http://tacticrealtime.com/privacy/

Teads.TV https://teads.tv/privacy-policy/

TEEMO https://teemo.co/fr/confidentialite/

The Trade Desk https://www.thetradedesk.com/general/privacy-policy

Tradedoubler http://www.tradedoubler.com/en/privacy-policy/

travel audience – An Amadeus Company https://travelaudience.com/product-privacy-policy/

TreSensa http://tresensa.com/eu-privacy/index.html

TripleLift https://triplelift.com/privacy/

TruEffect https://trueffect.com/privacy-policy/

TrustArc https://www.trustarc.com/privacy-policy/

Turbobytes https://www.turbobytes.com/gdpr/

UDG https://www.udg.de/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/privacy_policy_EN.pdf

usemax (Emego GmbH) http://www.usemax.de/?l=privacy

Videology https://videologygroup.com/en/privacy-policy/

Vimeo https://vimeo.com/cookie_policy

Virtual Minds https://virtualminds.de/datenschutz/

Vodafone GmbH https://www.vodafone.de/unternehmen/datenschutz-privatsphaere.html

Waystack https://www.wayfair.com/customerservice/general_info.php#privacy

Weborama https://weborama.com/e-privacy/

White Ops https://www.whiteops.com/privacy

Widespace https://www.widespace.com/legal/privacy-policy-notice/

WPP https://www.groupm.com/mplatform-privacy-policy

Yieldr https://www.yieldr.com/privacy/

ZMS https://zms.zalando.com/#
